
export const animeQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Who is known as the Pirate King in One Piece?",
        answers: {
            a: "Monkey D. Luffy",
            b: "Gol D. Roger",
            c: "Edward Newgate",
            d: "Shanks"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Goku's signature attack in Dragon Ball?",
        answers: {
            a: "Spirit Bomb",
            b: "Destructo Disk",
            c: "Kamehameha",
            d: "Final Flash"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "In Naruto, what is the Sharingan?",
        answers: {
            a: "A ninja weapon",
            b: "A type of jutsu",
            c: "A dojutsu (eye technique)",
            d: "A clan symbol"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the primary goal of the Survey Corps in Attack on Titan?",
        answers: {
            a: "To protect the king",
            b: "To explore the outside world",
            c: "To fight titans and reclaim territory",
            d: "To train soldiers"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the protagonist in Death Note?",
        answers: {
            a: "Light Yagami",
            b: "L Lawliet",
            c: "Ryuk",
            d: "Misa Amane"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Edward Elric's nickname in Fullmetal Alchemist?",
        answers: {
            a: "The Flame Alchemist",
            b: "The Fullmetal Alchemist",
            c: "The Steel Alchemist",
            d: "The State Alchemist"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ichigo's weapon in Bleach?",
        answers: {
            a: "Zanpakuto",
            b: "Bankai",
            c: "Quincy Bow",
            d: "Hollow Mask"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    },
    {
        question: "In My Hero Academia, what is Deku's real name?",
        answers: {
            a: "Katsuki Bakugo",
            b: "Todoroki Shoto",
            c: "Izuku Midoriya",
            d: "Tenya Iida"
        },
        correctAnswer: "c"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the main focus of the anime Haikyuu!!?",
        answers: {
            a: "Basketball",
            b: "Volleyball",
            c: "Soccer",
            d: "Tennis"
        },
        correctAnswer: "b"
    },
    {
        question: "In Sword Art Online, what is Kirito's real name?",
        answers: {
            a: "Kazuto Kirigaya",
            b: "Kirigaya Suguha",
            c: "Asuna Yuuki",
            d: "Klein"
        },
        correctAnswer: "a"
    }
];

